[{"question": "What is the output of C Program with Switch Statement.?\nint main()\n{\n    \n    int a=5;\n    \n    switch(a)\n    {\n        case 0: printf(\"0 \");\n        case 3: printf(\"3 \");\n        case 5: printf(\"5 \");\n        default: printf(\"RABBIT \");\n    }\n    \n    a=10;\n    switch(a)\n    {\n        case 0: printf(\"0 \");\n        case 3: printf(\"3 \");\n        case 5: printf(\"5 \");\n        default: printf(\"RABBIT \"); break;\n    }\n    \n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) 5 RABBIT", "option2": "B) 0 3 5 RABBIT 0 3 5 RABBIT", "option3": "C) 0 3 5 RABBIT RABBIT", "option4": "D) 3 5 RABBIT RABBIT", "ans": "D"}, {"question": "What is the output of C Program with switch statement.?\nint main()\n{\n    int a=3;\n    \n    switch(a)\n    {\n        case 2: printf(\"ZERO \"); break;\n\n        case default: printf(\"RABBIT \");\n    }\n    \n}\n", "option1": "A) RABBIT", "option2": "B) ZERO RABBIT", "option3": "C) No output", "option4": "D) Compiler error", "ans": "D"}, {"question": "What is the output of C Program with switch statement or block.?\nint main()\n{\n    int a=3;\n    \n    switch(a)\n    {\n\n    }\n    \n    printf(\"MySwitch\");\n}\n", "option1": "A) MySwitch", "option2": "B) No Output", "option3": "C) Compiler Error", "option4": "D) None of the above", "ans": "A"}, {"question": "What is the output of C Program with switch statement or block.?\nint main()\n{\n    int a;\n    \n    switch(a)\n    {\n        printf(\"APACHE \");\n    }\n    \n    printf(\"HEROHONDA\");\n}\n", "option1": "A) APACHE HEROHONDA", "option2": "B) HEROHONDA", "option3": "C) No Output", "option4": "D) Compiler error", "ans": "B"}, {"question": "What is the output of C program with switch statement or block.?\nint main()\n{\n    int a;\n    \n    switch(a);\n    {\n        printf(\"DEER \");\n    }\n    \n    printf(\"LION\");\n}\n", "option1": "A) LION", "option2": "B) DEER LION", "option3": "C) Compiler error", "option4": "D) None of the above", "ans": "B"}, {"question": "What is the output of C Program with switch statement or block.?\nint main()\n{\n    static int a=5;\n    \n    switch(a)\n    {\n        case 0: printf(\"ZERO \");break;\n        case 5: printf(\"FIVE \");break;\n        case 10: printf(\"DEER \");\n    }\n    \n    printf(\"LION\");\n}\n", "option1": "A) ZERO FIVE DEER LION", "option2": "B) FIVE DEER LION", "option3": "C) FIVE LION", "option4": "D) Compiler error", "ans": "C"}, {"question": "What is the output of C program with switch statement or block.?\nint main()\n{\n    char code='K';\n    \n    switch(code)\n    {\n        case 'A': printf(\"ANT \");break;\n        case 'K': printf(\"KING \"); break;\n        default: printf(\"NOKING\");\n    }\n    \n    printf(\"PALACE\");\n}\n", "option1": "A) KING PALACE", "option2": "B) KING NOTHING PALACE", "option3": "C) ANT KING PALACE", "option4": "D) Compiler error for using Non Integers as CASE constants.", "ans": "A"}, {"question": "What is the output of C Program with switch statement or block.?\nint main()\n{\n    char code='K';\n    \n    switch(code)\n    {\n        case \"A\": printf(\"ANT \");break;\n        case \"K\": printf(\"KING \"); break;\n        default: printf(\"NOKING\");\n    }\n    \n    printf(\"PALACE\");\n}\n", "option1": "A) ANT KING PALACE", "option2": "B) KING PALACE", "option3": "C) PALACE", "option4": "D) Compiler error", "ans": "D"}, {"question": "What is the output of C Program with switch statement\u00a0or block.?\nint main()\n{\n    char code='A';\n    \n    switch(code)\n    {\n        case 64+1: printf(\"ANT \");break;\n        case 8*8+4: printf(\"KING \"); break;\n        default: printf(\"NOKING\");\n    }\n    \n    printf(\"PALACE\");\n}\n", "option1": "A) ANT KING PALACE", "option2": "B) KING PALACE", "option3": "C) ANT PALACE", "option4": "D) Compiler error for using expressions", "ans": "C"}, {"question": " What is the output of C Program with switch statement or block.?\nint main()\n{\n    char code=64;\n    \n    switch(code)\n    {\n        case 64: printf(\"SHIP \");break;\n        case 8*8: printf(\"BOAT \"); break;\n        default: printf(\"PETROL\");\n    }\n    \n    printf(\"CHILLY\");\n}\n", "option1": "A) SHIP CHILLY", "option2": "B) BOAT CHILLY", "option3": "C) BOAT PETROL CHILLY", "option4": "D) Compiler error", "ans": "D"}, {"question": " What is the output of C Program with switch statement or block.?\nint main()\n{\n    int k=64;\n    \n    switch(k)\n    {\n        case k<64: printf(\"SHIP \");break;\n        case k>=64: printf(\"BOAT \"); break;\n        default: printf(\"PETROL\");\n    }\n    \n    printf(\"CHILLY\");\n}\n", "option1": "A) BOAT CHILLY", "option2": "B) BOAT PETROL CHILLY", "option3": "C) SHIP BOAT CHILLY", "option4": "D) Compiler error", "ans": "D"}, {"question": " What is the output of C Program with switch statement or block.?\nint main()\n{\n    int k=8;\n    \n    switch(k)\n    {\n        case 1==8: printf(\"ROSE \");break;\n        case 1 && 2: printf(\"JASMINE \"); break;\n        default: printf(\"FLOWER \");\n    }\n    \n    printf(\"GARDEN\");\n}\n", "option1": "A) ROSE GARGEN", "option2": "B) JASMINE GARDEN", "option3": "C) FLOWER GARDEN", "option4": "D) Compiler error", "ans": "C"}, {"question": " What is the output of C Program with switch statement or block.?\nint main()\n{\n    int k=25;\n    \n    switch(k)\n    {\n        case 24: printf(\"ROSE \");break;\n        case 25: printf(\"JASMINE \"); continue;\n        default: printf(\"FLOWER \");\n    }\n    \n    printf(\"GARDEN\");\n}\n", "option1": "A) JASMINE GARDEN", "option2": "B) JASMINE FLOWER GARDEN", "option3": "C) FLOWER GARDEN", "option4": "D) Compiler error", "ans": "D"}, {"question": " What is the output of C Program with switch statement or block.?\nint main()\n{\n    switch(24.5)\n    {\n        case 24.5: printf(\"SILVER \");break;\n        case 25.0: printf(\"GOLD \"); break;\n        default: printf(\"TIN \");\n    }\n    \n    printf(\"COPPER\");\n}\n", "option1": "A) SILVER COPPER", "option2": "B) TIN COPPER", "option3": "C) COPPER", "option4": "D) Compiler error", "ans": "D"}, {"question": " Choose a correct statement about a C Switch Construct.", "option1": "A) default case is optional inside switch.", "option2": "B) break; causes the control to exit the switch immediately and avoid fall down to other CASE statements.", "option3": "C) You can not use duplicate CASE Constants inside a Switch construct.", "option4": "D) All the above.", "ans": "D"}]
